{
"question": "皆",
"answer": "みんな"
},
{
"question": "新しい",
"answer": "あたらしい"
},
{
"question": "話",
"answer": "はなし"
},
{
"question": "明日",
"answer": "あした"
},
{
"question": "昨日",
"answer": "きのう"
},
{
"question": "出る",
"answer": "でる"
},
{
"question": "勉強",
"answer": "べんきょう"
},
{
"question": "取る",
"answer": "とる"
},
{
"question": "誰",
"answer": "だれ"
},
{
"question": "お金",
"answer": "おかね"
},
{
"question": "男",
"answer": "おとこ"
},
{
"question": "犬",
"answer": "いぬ"
},
{
"question": "使う",
"answer": "つかう"
},
{
"question": "大変",
"answer": "たいへん"
},
{
"question": "待つ",
"answer": "まつ"
},
{
"question": "作る",
"answer": "つくる"
},
{
"question": "後ろ",
"answer": "うしろ"
},
{
"question": "町",
"answer": "まち"
},
{
"question": "駅",
"answer": "えき"
},
{
"question": "少し",
"answer": "すこし"
},
